cyberwebsearch.com 2006-06-16

# Private Policy - Cyber Web Search

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only in effect for the Web Sites, newsletters, discussion groups and opt-in announcement lists, etc. owned and operated by Cyberwebsearch. 

**What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?**  
Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web Site within the Cyberwebsearch Network, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our Site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, but do not collect and evaluate this information for individuals. Our Web servers do not record e-mail addresses of the visitors. 

**What are cookies?**  
From time to time, Cyberwebsearch or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of Cyberwebsearch's Network of Web sites you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. Our advertisers and we may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our Sites.  
You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. 

**What information do You collect when I register for something?**  
Cyberwebsearch offers access to some services that are free but that require registration. We may use your contact information to send notification of Cyberwebsearch products and services by e-mail and/or postal mail. We also may share that information with our clients. Our clients may send you promotional material that is related to the topic of the service for which you registered if you have opted to receive it. 

**What other information do you request?**  
We may also request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a survey or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters, announcement lists or information about seminars). Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent. 

**What information do you collect when I purchase something?**  
If you are purchasing something from an Cyberwebsearch, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. This information may also be used by us to notify you of related product and services. Credit card and e-mail information will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose without your express permission. 

**Correspondence:**  
If you contact Cyberwebsearch, we may keep a record of that correspondence. We do not collect any email addresses of those who communicate with Cyberwebsearch via email. We use the information provided so that we may respond to the email. 

**Prevent others from using your account**  
On some Sites Of Cyberwebsearch, cookies help us efficiently determine that only one user is logged on under the same member name at a time. 

**Special Attention to Children**  
Cyberwebsearch, takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of young people using our services. We do not specifically collect information about children and believe that children should get their parents' consent before giving out any personal information. We encourage you to participate in your child's experience and to review our important safety tips before your child explores the Internet.

**Your Consent To This Agreement**  
By using Cyberwebsearch, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Questions regarding the above statement should be directed to Cyberwebsearch. [**Contact**](mailto:Sysadmin@cyberwebsearch.com)
